(Penny:)So you're okay?
(Howard:)Hey, I'm a big boy.
(Howard:)I'm not traumatized by some random
comment from some random woman.
(Howard:)I mean, get over yourself.
(Penny:)Okay. Well...
(Howard:)...bye.
[HOWARD SOBBING]
(Penny:)So close.
[CRASHING ON COMPUTER]
(Leonard:)Oh, my God. That's Kripke's robot?
KRIPKE [ON COMPUTER]:
As you can see...
...the Crippler is reducing
the Chevy Cavalier to rubble.
(Raj:)I can't watch anymore.
- Sheldon, we have to call it off.
- We don't have that option.
(Sheldon:)We've accepted the challenge.
We can't run away from a fight.
(Leonard:)Oh, please. We've spent our whole lives
running away from fights.
(Leonard:)Personally, I can squeeze through
a hole in a fence half my size.